<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>darek.blog</title>
    <link>https://darek.blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on darek.blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darek.blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>https://darek.blog/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 13:56:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darek.blog/privacy/</guid>
      <description>You are safe with me!
I do not collect any of your private data through this blog, neither I allow anything to track you.
If you want to get in touch, just write me an email to EMAIL
Sometimes your web browser may save cookies, but you can always turn them off in your browser settings. Learn how to do it HERE
Explore the content of this blog with the peace of mind!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://darek.blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 11:15:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darek.blog/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Dariusz Grzemny and I am a youth worker, a trainer, sometimes a project manager and a writer (nowadays I write more than I train people).
I work in the Association for Children and Young People CHANCE in Głogów (Poland) where I mainly manage youth projects on anti-discrimination, anti-racism and human rights education. I am also a freelance trainer involved in various (mainly international) activities. Recently, I have also started podcasting and I find it really amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my blog</title>
      <link>https://darek.blog/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darek.blog/posts/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>I am starting my blog. Finally! I have thought about it for a long time, and I am not really sure what was stopping me from doing it. But here I am with my blog!
I developed this blog using Hugo, a wonderful and very flexible framework for building websites. It is open-source and it generates static websites. Well, static does not mean that nothing will change here. Quite on the contrary, I plan to put different stuff in here:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
